Guide to the Maria Mitchell Papers, 1843-2016 (bulk 1853-1889)
Vassar College Libraries Archives and Special Collections
- SERIES X. GLASS PLATE NEGATIVES, 1871-1890
  - Observed by Whitney and Richmond, 1883 Oct 9 [12:15 PM?] (Neg. Box 20)
  - Observed by Whitney and Richmond, 1883 Oct 10 [12:15 PM?] (Neg. Box 15)
  - Observed by Whitney and Richmond, 1883 Oct 11 12:11 PM; [envelope only] (Neg. Box 15)
  - Observed by Whitney and Richmond, 1883 Oct 15 12:08 PM (Neg. Box 15)
  - Observed by Whitney and Richmond, 1883 Oct 16 12:23 PM (Neg. Box 23)
  - Observed by Whitney and Richmond, 1883 Oct 17 12:11 PM (Neg. Box 23)
  - Observed by Whitney, 1883 Oct 19 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 23)
  - Observed by Whitney and Richmond, 1883 Oct 30 12:20 PM (Neg. Box 23)
  - Observed by Whitney and Richmond, 1883 Nov 5 12:11 PM (Neg. Box 20)
  - Observed by Whitney and Richmond, 1883 Nov 5 12:25 PM (Neg. Box 23)
  - Observed by Whitney and Richmond, 1883 Nov 7 12:30 PM (Neg. Box 15)
    Notes: "Poor Focus."
  - Observed by Whitney and Richmond, 1883 Nov 8 12:10 PM (Neg. Box 15)
  - Observed by Whitney and Richmond, 1883 Nov 15 [1:23 PM?]; [envelope only] (Neg. Box 14)
    Notes: "Duplicate. Cloudy"
  - Observed by Whitney and Richmond, 1883 Nov 15 12:13 PM (Neg. Box 15)
  - Observed by Whitney and Richmond, 1883 Nov 16 12:07 PM (Neg. Box 15)
  - Observed by Whitney and Richmond, 1883 Nov 17 12:27 PM (Neg. Box 15)
  - Observed by Whitney and Richmond, 1883 Nov 19 [12:20 PM?] (Neg. Box 6)
  - Observed by Whitney and Richmond, 1883 Nov 19 12:25 PM (Neg. Box 15)
    Notes: "Cloudy."
  - Observed by Whitney and Richmond, 1883 Nov 27 12:04 PM (Neg. Box 19)
    Notes: "Poor negative"
  - Observed by Whitney and Richmond, 1883 Dec 3 12:14 PM (Neg. Box 15)
  - Observed by Whitney and Richmond, 1883 Dec 10 12:13 PM (Neg. Box 15)
  - Observed by Whitney and Richmond, 1883 Dec 11 12:13 PM (Neg. Box 15)
  - Observed by Whitney and Richmond, 1884 Jan 10 12:15 PM (Neg. Box 30)
    Notes: "Poor negative – Thermometer 27"
  - Observed by Whitney and Richmond, 1884 Jan 16 12:11 PM (Neg. Box 30)
    Notes: "Negative poor. Very cold; about 15"
  - Observed by Whitney, 1884 Jan 18 [1:30 PM?] (Neg. Box 30)
  - Observed by Whitney and Richmond, 1884 Feb 15 12:11 PM (Neg. Box 30)
  - Observed by Whitney and Richmond, 1884 Feb 15 12:09 PM (Neg. Box 30)
  - Observed by Whitney and Deming, 1884 Feb 22 12:22 PM (Neg. Box 13)
  - Observed by Whitney and Deming, 1884 Mar 10 12:12 PM (Neg. Box 30)
  - Observed by Whitney and Gardner, 1884 Mar 16 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 30)
  - Observed by Whitney and Deming, 1884 Mar 25 12:07 PM (Neg. Box 20)
    Notes: "Poor negative. Duplicate."
  - Observed by Whitney and Deming, 1884 Mar 25 12:17 PM (Neg. Box 32)
  - Observed by Whitney and Deming, 1884 Mar 28 12:12 PM (Neg. Box 32)
  - Observed by Whitney and Deming, 1884 Mar 29 12:28 PM (Neg. Box 32)
  - Observed by Whitney and Deming, 1884 Apr 1 12:21 PM (Neg. Box 32)
    Notes: "Poor negative "
  - Observed by Whitney and Deming, 1884 Apr 7 12:15 PM (Neg. Box 32)
    Notes: "Cloudy – Poorly varnished"
  - Observed by Whitney and Deming, 1884 Apr 21 [1:29 PM?] (Neg. Box 32)
  - Observed by Whitney and Wheeler, 1884 Apr 27 10:15 AM (Neg. Box 32)
  - Observed by Whitney and Deming, 1884 Apr 29 12:12 PM (Neg. Box 32)
    Notes: "Plate fogged."
  - Observed by Whitney and Deming, 1884 Apr 30 11:53 AM (Neg. Box 32)
  - Observed by Whitney and Deming, 1884 May 14 11:56 AM (Neg. Box 30)
    Notes: "First dry plate used. Considerably fogged."
  - Observed by Whitney and Deming, 1884 May 15 12:15 PM (Neg. Box 30)
    Notes: "Second dry plate used. Faint negative."
  - Observed by Whitney and Deming, 1884 May 19 12:07 PM (Neg. Box 30)
  - Observed by Whitney and Deming, 1884 May 21 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 30)
    Notes: "2 Cal (?)"
  - Observed by Whitney and Lucas, 1884 May 24 11:45 AM (Neg. Box 30)
  - Observed by Whitney and Gould, 1884 May 28 12:03 PM (Neg. Box 30)
    Notes: "Poor. "
  - Observed by Whitney and Gould, 1884 May 29 (Neg. Box 30)
  - Observed by Whitney and Gould, 1884 May 31 12:10 PM (Neg. Box 30)
    Notes: "Good "
  - Observed by Whitney and Gould, 1884 Jun 2 11:55 AM (Neg. Box 30)
  - Observed by Whitney and Gould, 1884 Jun 4 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 30)
  - Observed by Whitney and Gould, 1884 Jun 5 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 30)
  - Observed by Whitney and Gould, 1884 Jun 7 12:30 PM (Neg. Box 30)
  - Observed by Whitney and Gould, 1884 Jun 9 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 30)
    Notes: "Focus Poor."
  - Observed by Whitney and Davis, 1884 Oct 1 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 12)
  - Observed by Whitney and Davis, 1884 Oct 4 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 11)
  - Observed by Whitney and Davis, 1884 Oct 6 11:10 AM (Neg. Box 11)
  - Observed by Whitney and Davis, 1884 Oct 7 12:05 PM (Neg. Box 11)
  - Observed by Whitney and Davis, 1884 Oct 9 [12:00 PM?] (Neg. Box 12)
  - Observed by Whitney and Davis, 1884 Oct 10 [12:00 PM?] (Neg. Box 12)
    Notes: "Show better by reflected light"
  - Sunspots, observed by Whitney and Lingle, 1884 Oct 15 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 11)
    Notes: "Group of two spots—on following edge. Poor."
  - Sunspots, observed by Whitney and Davis, 1884 Oct 17 11:50 AM (Neg. Box 12)
    Notes: "Poor—Two spots on following limb—cloudy"
  - Sunspots, observed by Whitney and Lingle, 1884 Oct 20 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 12)
    Notes: "Poor—Some – in exposure or focus that I do not understand"
  - Observed by Whitney and Lingle, 1884 Oct 22 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 12)
  - Observed by Whitney and Lingle, 1884 Oct 24 11:50 AM (Neg. Box 12)
  - Observed by Whitney and Lingle, 1884 Oct 29 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 12)
  - Observed by Whitney and Lingle, 1884 Nov 3 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 13)
  - Observed by Whitney and Lingle, 1884 Nov 6 12:05 PM (Neg. Box 32)
    Notes: "Used the full opening of the beam --"
  - Observed by Whitney and Davis, 1884 Nov 10 12:15 PM (Neg. Box 32)
    Notes: "Used an opening slightly smaller than the full aperture marked a"
  - Observed by Whitney and Davis, 1884 Nov 11 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 13)
    Notes: "Full aperture "
  - Observed by Whitney and Davis, 1884 Nov 13 11:55 AM (Neg. Box 12)
  - Observed by Whitney and Witkowsky, 1884 Nov 14 12:05 PM (Neg. Box 12)
    Notes: "Hazy. Full aperture."
  - Observed by Whitney and Lingle, 1884 Nov 17 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 12)
    Notes: "Full aperture – Position of stand, a-"
  - Observed by Whitney and Lingle, 1884 Nov 18 11:47 AM (Neg. Box 12)
  - Observed by Whitney and Lingle, 1884 Nov 21 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 3)
    Notes: "Full aperture."
  - Observed by Whitney and Lingle, 1884 Nov 22 12:00 AM (Neg. Box 30)
    Notes: "Diaphram b_ Position b."
  - Observed by Whitney and Southworth, 1885 (Neg. Box 21)
    Notes: "(Oxalal-- developer weak -- and a --)"
  - Observed by Whitney and Canfield, 1885 Jan 13 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 33)
    Notes: "Thermometer, +5"
  - Observed by Whitney and Canfield, 1885 Jan 18 12:05 PM (Neg. Box 33)
  - Observed by Whitney and Canfield, 1885 Feb 1 12:05 PM (Neg. Box 33)
  - Observed by Whitney and Canfield, 1885 Feb 2 12:05 PM (Neg. Box 33)
  - Observed by Whitney and Royce, 1885 Feb 8 12:05 PM (Neg. Box 13)
  - Observed by Whitney and Canfield, 1885 Feb 9 12:04 PM (Neg. Box 33)
  - Observed by Whitney and Wilson, 1885 Mar 4 12:08 PM (Neg. Box 33)
    Notes: "Defective plate. (This package of plates is very poor)"
  - Observed by Whitney and Wilson, 1885 Mar 4 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 33)
    Notes: "Defective plate."
  - Observed by Whitney and Witkowsky, 1885 Mar 5 12:08 PM (Neg. Box 33)
    Notes: "Position a"
  - Observed by Whitney and Wilson, 1885 Mar 6 11:55 AM (Neg. Box 33)
  - Observed by Whitney and Witkowsky, 1885 Mar 14 12:10 PM (Neg. Box 13)
    Notes: "Full aperture – position a – poor focus."
  - Solar Eclipse, observed by Whitney and Southworth, 1885 Mar 16; [envelope only] (Neg. Box 14)
    Notes: "Solar Eclipse"
  - Solar Eclipse, observed by Whitney and Southworth, 1885 Mar 16 (Neg. Box 36.20)
    Notes: "Eclipse no. 2"
  - Solar Eclipse, observed by Whitney and Witkowsky, 1885 Mar 16 (Neg. Box 36.21)
    Notes: "Eclipse no. 3"
  - Solar Eclipse, observed by Whitney and Witkowsky, 1885 Mar 16 (Neg. Box 36.19)
    Notes: "Eclipse no. 4"
  - Solar Eclipse, observed by Whitney and Witkowsky, 1885 Mar 16 (Neg. Box 36.22)
    Notes: "Eclipse no. 5"
  - Observed by Whitney and Southworth, 1885 Mar 26 12:08 PM (Neg. Box 11)
  - Observed by Whitney and Southworth, 1885 Mar 28 11:58 AM (Neg. Box 11)
    Notes: "Poor. New Belgian plate. Aperture c."
  - Observed by Whitney and Southworth, 1885 Mar 30 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 11)
    Notes: "-- plate aperture a."
  - Observed by Whitney and Canfield, 1885 Apr 1 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 33)
  - Observed by Whitney and Witkowsky, 1885 Apr 9 12:03 PM (Neg. Box 13)
    Notes: "Full aperture v. slow movement. Fogged."
  - Observed by Whitney and Wilson, 1885 Apr 10 12:04 PM (Neg. Box 5)
  - Observed by Whitney and Southworth, 1885 Apr 16 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 13)
  - Observed by Whitney and Southworth, 1885 Apr 17 11:55 AM (Neg. Box 13)
  - Sunspots, observed by Whitney and Davis, 1885 Apr 18 12:30 PM (Neg. Box 36.18)
    Notes: "- plate developer used."
  - Observed by Whitney and Davis, 1885 Apr 19 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 13)
  - Observed by Whitney and Southworth, 1885 Apr 20 11:55 AM (Neg. Box 13)
  - Observed by Whitney and Southworth, 1885 Apr 22 11:56 AM (Neg. Box 11)
    Notes: "Plate slightly marred."
  - Observed by Whitney and Southworth, 1885 Apr 23 11:57 AM (Neg. Box 13)
  - Sunspots, observed by Whitney and Southworth, 1885 Apr 24 11:58 AM (Neg. Box 36.17)
    Notes: "Carbutt plate. At Lana developer."
  - Observed by Whitney and Southworth, 1885 Apr 25 12:23 PM (Neg. Box 13)
  - Observed by Whitney and Southworth, 1885 Apr 27 11:59 AM (Neg. Box 13)
  - Sunspots, observed by Palmer and Davis, 1885 Apr 30 11:58 AM (Neg. Box 36.12)
  - Observed by Whitney and Southworth, 1885 May 2 11:54 AM (Neg. Box 5)
  - Observed by Whitney and Southworth, 1885 May 6 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 20)
    Notes: "Too faint by direct light. Shows well by reflected light."
  - Observed by Whitney and Witkowsky, 1885 May 9 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 11)
  - Observed by Whitney and Southworth, 1885 May 15 11:58 AM (Neg. Box 11)
  - Observed by Whitney and Southworth, 1885 May 19 11:48 AM; [envelope only] (Neg. Box 14)
  - Observed by Whitney and Baker, 1885 May 21 [1:30 PM?] (Neg. Box 11)
  - Observed by Whitney and Southworth, 1885 May 26 11:58 AM (Neg. Box 11)
    Notes: "Hazy."
  - Observed by Whitney and Southworth, 1885 May 28 11:58 AM (Neg. Box 11)
  - Observed by Whitney and Buck, 1885 May 29 11:56 AM (Neg. Box 5)
  - Observed by Whitney and Buck, 1885 Jun 1 11:59 AM (Neg. Box 11)
  - Observed by Whitney and Southworth, 1885 Jun 2 11:51 AM; [envelope only] (Neg. Box 19)
  - Sunspots, observed by Whitney and Macy, 1885 Jun 8 [12:00 PM?] (Neg. Box 36.13)
  - Observed by Whitney, 1885 Jun 9 [12:00 PM?] (Neg. Box 5)
  - Observed by Whitney and Canfield, 1885 Sep 25 12:13 PM (Neg. Box 12)
  - Observed by Whitney and Canfield, 1885 Sep 28 12:15 PM (Neg. Box 12)
  - Observed by Whitney and Canfield, 1885 Oct 1 [12:00 PM?] (Neg. Box 12)
    Notes: "Poor plate very defective."
  - Observed by Whitney and Canfield, 1885 Oct 5 11:20 AM (Neg. Box 2)
  - Sunspots, observed by Whitney and Canfield, 1885 Oct 9 12:10 PM (Neg. Box 36.16)
  - Observed by Whitney and Canfield, 1885 Oct 10 12:03 PM (Neg. Box 12)
  - Sunspots, observed by Whitney and Royce, 1885 Oct 17 12:10 PM (Neg. Box 18)
    Notes: "Two very small spots precede the large group on following edge."
  - Observed by Whitney and Canfield, 1885 Oct 19 12:02 PM (Neg. Box 18)
  - Observed by Whitney and Royce, 1885 Oct 23 12:10 PM (Neg. Box 11)
  - Observed by Whitney and Royce, 1885 Oct 24 12:15 PM (Neg. Box 11)
  - Observed by Whitney and Royce, 1885 Oct 26 12:10 PM (Neg. Box 12)
    Notes: "Very defective plate."
  - Observed by Whitney and Jenckes, 1885 Oct 27 12:05 PM (Neg. Box 11)
  - Observed by Whitney and Canfield, 1885 Oct 28 [12:00 PM?] (Neg. Box 11)
  - Observed by Whitney and Canfield, 1885 Oct 31 circa 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 11)
  - Observed by Whitney and Canfield, 1885 Oct 31 [12:00 PM?] (Neg. Box 12)
    Notes: "Plate defective"
  - Observed by Whitney and Canfield, 1885 Nov 2 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 11)
  - Observed by Whitney and Canfield, 1885 Nov 9 1:45 PM?] (Neg. Box 11)
  - Observed by Whitney and Canfield, 1885 Nov 13 11:45 AM (Neg. Box 11)
  - Observed by Whitney and Canfield, 1885 Nov 15 12:20 PM (Neg. Box 11)
  - Observed by Whitney and Royce, 1885 Nov 16 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 11)
  - Observed by Whitney and Canfield, 1885 Nov 17 (Neg. Box 11)
  - Observed by Whitney and Canfield, 1885 Nov 20 12:03 PM (Neg. Box 11)
  - Sunspots, observed by Whitney and Canfield, 1885 Dec 2 12:05 PM (Neg. Box 18)
    Notes: "A faint group only."
  - Observed by Whitney and Canfield, 1885 Dec 11 12:10 PM (Neg. Box 18)
    Notes: "Rather poor definition."
  - Observed by [unknown], 1885 Dec 15 12:02 PM (Neg. Box 12)
  - Observed by Whitney and Canfield, 1886 Jan 8 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 13)
  - Observed by Whitney and Canfield, 1886 Jan 12 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 33)
    Notes: "Very poor – Perhaps Discard. Thermometer, -1"
  - Observed by Whitney and Canfield, 1886 Jan 15 12:05 PM (Neg. Box 33)
  - Sunspots, observed by Gardner and Metcalf, 1886 Feb 5 (Neg. Box 14)
    Notes: "No spots. On Feb 3 and Feb. 4 no spots could be found. Feb. 8 No spots (plate destroyed)."
  - Observed by Whitney and Canfield, 1886 Feb 10 12:05 PM (Neg. Box 33)
  - Sunspots, observed by Whitney and Wilson, 1886 Feb 16 12:10 PM (Neg. Box 33)
    Notes: "One spot close on following edge with faculae and small spots (hardly seen in negative) about – Cloudy"
  - Sunspots, observed by Whitney and Wilson, 1886 Feb 18 12:11 PM (Neg. Box 13)
    Notes: "One small group coming in. Poor plate."
  - Observed by Whitney and Wilson, 1886 Mar 1 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 13)
    Notes: "Defective plate"
  - Observed by Whitney and Wilson, 1886 Mar 3 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 33)
  - Observed by Whitney and Wilson, 1886 Mar 10 12:03 PM (Neg. Box 33)
  - Observed by Whitney and Wilson, 1886 Mar 11 12:03 PM (Neg. Box 33)
    Notes: "Poor – another at 2h, also poor."
  - Observed by Whitney and Wilson, 1886 Mar 15 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 33)
  - Observed by Whitney and Wilson, 1886 Mar 16 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 13)
  - Observed by Whitney and Wilson, 1886 Apr 9 12:03 PM (Neg. Box 33)
  - Observed by Whitney and Wilson, 1886 Apr 15 12:03 PM (Neg. Box 33)
  - Observed by Whitney and Wilson, 1886 Apr 16 12:10 PM (Neg. Box 33)
  - Observed by Whitney and Wilson, 1886 Apr 17 11:45 AM (Neg. Box 33)
  - Observed by Whitney and Wilson, 1886 Apr 19 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 33)
  - Observed by Whitney and Bradley, 1886 Apr 22 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 33)
  - Observed by Whitney and Wilson, 1886 Apr 22 12:03 PM (Neg. Box 33)
  - Observed by Whitney and Bradley, 1886 Apr 23 12:07 PM (Neg. Box 33)
  - Observed by [unknown], 1886 May 2 9:15 AM (Neg. Box 33)
  - Sunspots, observed by Whitney and Bradley, 1886 May 3 12:09 PM (Neg. Box 2)
    Notes: "Sun spots"
  - Observed by Whitney and Bradley, 1886 May 6 [12:00 PM?] (Neg. Box 2)
  - Observed by Whitney and Bradley, 1886 May 7 11:53 AM (Neg. Box 33)
    Notes: "Quite cloudy."
  - Observed by Whitney and Bradley, 1886 May 21 11:58 AM (Neg. Box 33)
  - Observed by Whitney and Bradley, 1886 May 28 11:55 AM (Neg. Box 33)
  - Observed by Whitney and Hoffin (?), 1886 May 30 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 13)
  - Observed by Whitney and Bradley, 1886 May 31 12:25 PM (Neg. Box 13)
  - Observed by Whitney and Bradley, 1886 Jun 1 11:53 AM (Neg. Box 13)
  - Observed by Whitney and Bradley, 1886 Jun 4 11:54 AM (Neg. Box 33)
  - Observed by Whitney and Bradley, 1886 Jun 5 11:45 AM (Neg. Box 5)
  - Observed by Whitney and Bradley, 1886 Jun 8 11:56 AM (Neg. Box 25)
    Notes: "Poorly varnished and cracked"
  - Observed by Whitney and MacCreery, 1886 Oct 5 12:07 PM (Neg. Box 21)
  - Observed by Whitney and Royce, 1886 Oct 6 12:03 PM (Neg. Box 21)
  - Sunspots, observed by Whitney and MacCreery, 1886 Oct 8 12:07 PM (Neg. Box 21)
    Notes: "Following group – to small spots, hardly seen in negative."
  - Sunspots, observed by Whitney and MacCreery, 1886 Oct 11 12:07 PM (Neg. Box 21)
    Notes: "Poor negative. Two or Three very small spots near middle"
  - Observed by Whitney and Maury, 1886 Oct 21 12:05 PM (Neg. Box 21)
  - Observed by Whitney and MacCreery, 1886 Nov 16 12:07 PM (Neg. Box 21)
  - Observed by Whitney and Royce, 1886 Dec 11 12:20 PM (Neg. Box 21)
  - Observed by Whitney and McCreery, 1887 Jan 21 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 5)
  - Observed by Whitney and McCreery, 1887 Jan 27 12:49 PM (Neg. Box 5)
    Notes: "Poor. A different plate. Not Carbate(?) A."
  - Observed by Whitney and MacCreery, 1887 Jan 31 12:02 PM (Neg. Box 5)
    Notes: "Poor Not -, -. "
  - Observed by Whitney and MacCreery, 1887 Feb 4 12:09 PM (Neg. Box 5)
    Notes: "Poor. One – off. Two on following limb."
  - Sunspots, observed by Whitney and McCreery, 1887 Feb 17 12:15 PM (Neg. Box 5)
    Notes: "1 p, 1 very small [illegible] 2 spots"
  - Observed by Whitney and Poppenheim, 1887 Feb 25 [12:00 PM?] (Neg. Box 21)
  - Observed by Whitney and Poppenheim, 1887 Mar 19 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 5)
  - Sunspots, observed by Whitney and Poppenheim, 1887 Mar 27 12:05 PM (Neg. Box 21)
    Notes: "Three very small spots two of which can be seen in negative."
  - Sunspots, observed by Whitney and Poppenheim, 1887 Apr 20 12:10 PM (Neg. Box 5)
    Notes: "Poor plate. Two spots over limb."
  - Sunspots, observed by Whitney and Poppenheim, 1887 Apr 21 12:08 PM (Neg. Box 5)
    Notes: "Poor plate. One round spot."
  - Observed by Whitney and Poppenheim, 1887 Apr 22 12:17 PM (Neg. Box 5)
  - Observed by Poppenheim and Whitney, 1887 Apr 25 12:20 PM (Neg. Box 21)
  - Observed by Whitney and Poppenheim, 1887 Apr 27 12:20 PM (Neg. Box 18)
  - Observed by Whtiney and Poppenheim, 1887 May 2 12:20 PM (Neg. Box 18)
  - Observed by Poppenheim and Lewi, 1887 May 5 (Neg. Box 18)
  - Observed by Poppenheim and Lewi, 1887 May 9 11:59 AM (Neg. Box 18)
  - Observed by Whitney and Poppenheim, 1887 May 10 12:20 PM (Neg. Box 21)
    Notes: "Plate at first exposure had fallen out of place—Therefore a second exposure was made."
  - Observed by Poppenheim and Lewi, 1887 May 11 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 21)
    Notes: "Poorly varnished."
  - Observed by Whitney and Palmer, 1887 May 13 12:15 PM (Neg. Box 18)
    Notes: "Poor plate---also fogged."
  - Sunspots, observed by Gardner and Hagard, 1887 May 15 12:20 PM (Neg. Box 6)
    Notes: "A large spot on the western limb. On May 16 the spot was preceded by a very faint spot which was not seen on May 15. - May 19 a large spot was seen coming on. Clouds preventing observations from May 19 to May 24. When(?) a group of many small spots was seen near the(?) center. The spot seen May 19 had probably broken up and formed this group - On May 26 this group was -- -- on the western limb but was then very faint. - May 27. The group could not be found. - May 28-31 no spots (Plate destroyed) - June [1-2, 20] no spots (plates destroyed)"
  - Observed by Poppenheim and Lowe, 1887 May 17 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 18)
  - Observed by Poppenheim and Lewi, 1887 May 18 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 18)
    Notes: "New kind of plate. Eagle—Hazy."
  - Observed by Popperheim and Lewis, 1887 May 19 (Neg. Box 12)
  - Observed by Whitney and Palmer, 1887 May 20 12:10 PM (Neg. Box 18)
  - Observed by Whitney and Palmer, 1887 May 21 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 18)
  - Observed by Palmer and Greene, 1887 Nov 12 12:13 PM (Neg. Box 18)
    Notes: "Poor, branches of trees."
  - Sunspots, observed by Spalding, 1887 Dec 3 12:04 PM (Neg. Box 6)
    Notes: "Large spot going off on -- -- -- second seen."
  - Observed by Palmer and Gates, 1887 Dec 16 12:20 PM (Neg. Box 12)
    Notes: "Fault in varnish."
  - Observed by Palmer and Gates, 1887 Dec 19 12:08 PM (Neg. Box 18)
  - Observed by Palmer and Davis, 1888 Jan 18 12:12 PM (Neg. Box 5)
  - Observed by Palmer and Whitney, 1888 Feb 23 12:10 PM (Neg. Box 25)
  - Observed by Palmer and Whitney, 1888 Feb 24 12:08 PM (Neg. Box 25)
  - Observed by Palmer and Brown, 1888 Mar 9 12:12 PM (Neg. Box 25)
  - Observed by Palmer and Whitney, 1888 Mar 10 12:10 PM (Neg. Box 25)
  - Observed by Palmer and Brown, 1888 Mar 16 12:06 PM (Neg. Box 25)
  - Observed by Palmer and Brown, 1888 Mar 17 12:07 PM (Neg. Box 25)
  - Observed by Palmer and Brown, 1888 Mar 19 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 25)
  - Observed by Palmer and Brown, 1888 Apr 26 12:02 PM (Neg. Box 25)
  - Observed by Palmer and Greene, 1888 Apr 27 12:02 PM (Neg. Box 25)
  - Observed by Palmer and Brown, 1888 May 14 11:59 AM (Neg. Box 25)
    Notes: "Fault in varnishing."
  - Observed by Palmer and Tunnicliff, 1888 May 17 12:14 PM (Neg. Box 24)
  - Observed by Palmer and Greene, 1888 May 19 12:08 PM (Neg. Box 24)
  - Observed by Palmer and Tunnicliff, 1888 May 21 12:14 PM (Neg. Box 33)
  - Observed by Palmer and Tunnicliff, 1888 May 22 12:10 PM (Neg. Box 24)
    Notes: "Fault in closing aperture."
  - Observed by Palmer and Mace, 1888 Jun 8 12:12 PM (Neg. Box 24)
  - Sunspots, observed by Hodge and Bush, 1888 Oct 14 12:15 PM (Neg. Box 25)
    Notes: "The large group of spots which appeared Oct. 13 is photographed with faculae. A smaller group has just come on the Sun."
  - Sunspots, observed by Whitney and Mace, 1888 Nov 1 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 24)
    Notes: "No spot – Taken for practice."
  - Sunspots, observed by Whitney and Mace, 1888 Nov 7 circa 12:15 PM (Neg. Box 36.26)
    Notes: "Tree interfered"
  - Observed by Whitney and Mace, 1888 Nov 7 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 24)
  - Observed by Whitney and Mace, 1888 Nov 13 circa 12:30 PM (Neg. Box 24)
  - Observed by Whitney and Mace, 1888 Nov 13 circa 11:00 AM (Neg. Box 24)
  - Observed by Mace and Whitney, 1888 Nov 15 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 24)
  - Observed by Mace and Kavana, 1888 Nov 17 [12:12 PM?] (Neg. Box 24)
  - Observed by Mace and Kavana, 1888 Nov 20 12:35 PM (Neg. Box 24)
  - Sunspots, observed by Mace and Whitney, 1888 Nov 20 10:35 AM (Neg. Box 36.11)
  - Observed by Mace and Furness, 1888 Nov 21 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 24)
  - Sunspots, observed by Mace and Kavana, 1888 Nov 22 12:05 PM (Neg. Box 24)
    Notes: "Spot just passing off."
  - Observed by Mace and Furness, 1888 Nov 28 11:50 AM (Neg. Box 24)
  - Observed by Whitney and Kavanna, 1888 Nov 30 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 5)
    Notes: "Plate fell out of supports"
  - Observed by Whitney and Kavanna, 1888 Dec 1 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 5)
    Notes: "Cloudy Plate fogged. Pyro developer used."
  - Observed by Whitney and Kavanna, 1888 Dec 1 11:00 AM (Neg. Box 5)
    Notes: "Pyro developer used. Poor plate."
  - Observed by Whitney and Mace, 1888 Dec 5 circa 12:15 PM (Neg. Box 24)
  - Observed by Mace and Furness, 1888 Dec 7 12:35 PM (Neg. Box 5)
  - Observed by Mace and Kavana, 1888 Dec 15 12:05 PM (Neg. Box 5)
  - Observed by Mace and Kavana, 1888 Dec 19 12:05 PM (Neg. Box 5)
  - Observed by Mace and Kavana, 1889 Jan 16 12:20 PM (Neg. Box 24)
  - Sunspots, observed by Mace and Kavana, 1889 Jan 16 [12:12 PM?] (Neg. Box 24)
    Notes: "Sun very hazy"
  - Sunspots, observed by Mace and Kavana, 1889 Feb 1 12:05 PM (Neg. Box 18)
    Notes: "No. 2"
  - Sunspots, observed by Mace and Whitney, 1889 Feb 22 circa 12:30 PM (Neg. Box 18)
    Notes: "A very small spot follows the larger one."
  - Sunspots, observed by Mace and Furness, 1889 Feb 25 12:03 PM (Neg. Box 18)
    Notes: "Hazy. Three spots."
  - Observed by Whitney and Mace, 1889 Mar 1 11:58 AM (Neg. Box 21)
  - Observed by Mace and [unknown], 1889 Mar 6 12:05 PM (Neg. Box 21)
  - Observed by Mace and Kavana, 1889 Mar 12 12:01 PM (Neg. Box 21)
  - Observed by Whitney and Mace, 1889 Mar 14 11:58 AM (Neg. Box 21)
  - Sunspots, observed by Whitney and Poppenheim, 1889 Mar 31 12:03 PM (Neg. Box 21)
    Notes: "Small group, 3."
  - Sunspots, observed by Whitney and Mace, 1889 Apr 11 (Neg. Box 18)
    Notes: "Spot on following edge. Hazy."